BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2)
1952- 1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/002
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Collective labor agreements.
5833595
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 27, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Collective labor agreements - United States.; United States. Department of Labor. Bureau of Labor Statistics.
5833595
- Code no.2923: Babcock and Wilcox Company and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers, Local No. 900, 1961-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Code no.2924: Bay Area Metal Fabricators Association and International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 790, 1961-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Code no.2926: California Metal Trades Association and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, 1968- 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Code no.2927: Combustion Engineering, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers, Local No. 900, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Code no.2928: Employers Group of Steel Fabricators and International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 468, 1960-1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Code no.2929: Walworth Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Code no.2930: Hollow Metal Door and Buck Association, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 2947 AND New York City District Council of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Code no.2934: The R.C. Mahon Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1959-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Code no.2936: American Bridge Division, United States Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1967-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Code no.2937: Consolidated Western Steel Division of United States Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1960- 1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Code no.2938: The Lamson and Sessions Company and International Union of United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 217, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Code no.2939: The National Screw and Manufacturing Company and International Union of United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 843, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Code no.2940: Screw and Bolt Corporation of America and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Code no.2941: Commercial Shearing and Stamping Company and United Steelworkers of America, Locals 2332, 2757, 4732, 1960- 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Code no.2942: Mirro Aluminum Company and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Code no.2943: Owens-Illinois Glass Company and Glass Bottle Blowers Association of America, AFL-CIO, 1960-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Code no.2945: American Chain and Cable Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Code no.2947: Associated Spring Corporation and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 712, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Code no.2948: The Wm. Powell Co. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1858, 1958-1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Code no.2949: Rheem Manufacturing Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Code no.2950: Scovil Manufacturing Company and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, 1952- 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Code no.2953: The Budd Company and (The International Union of) United Auto Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Locals 92, 306, 813, 1122, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Code no.2954: The Budd Company and (The International Union of) United Auto Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Locals 92, 306, 813, 1122, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Code no.2955: McInerney Spring and Wire Co. and (The International Union of) United Auto Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 687, 1962- 1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Code no.2961: American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 1199, 1963- 1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Code no.2956: Boiler and Tank Contractors of Chicago and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers, Local No. 1, 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Code no.2962: Fisher Controls Company and International Union of United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 893, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Code no.2958: Crown Cork and Seal Company, Inc. and Can Workers' Union Local 266 (Affiliated with Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, AFL-CIO), 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Code no.2964: Standard Screw Company and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 59, 1965- 1971 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Code no.2966: Washington Metal Trades, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, Welders and Helpers of America, Local 104, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Code no.2968: Elastic Stop Nut Corporation of America and United Auto Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 726, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Code no.2969: Crown Cork and Seal Company, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 5267, 1964-1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Code no.2974: The Wire and Metal Products Manufacturers Guild, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 810, 1967- 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Code no.2975: Blaw-Knox Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1243, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Code no.2978: Foster Wheeler Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Local 1665, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Code no.3200: Alco Engine, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Locals 3440, 3482, 1960-1971 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Code no.3201: Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 1091, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Code no.3203: Briggs and Stratton Corporation and Allied Industrial Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 232, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Code no.3205: Clinton Engines Corporation and International Association of Machinists, AFL-CIO, Local 102, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Code no.3206: Continental Motors Corporation and International Union of United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 113, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Code no.1202: Marathon (Division of the American Can Company) and United Papermakers and Paper Workers, ALF-CIO, Local 327, 1959- 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Code no.1202: Marathon (Division of the American Can Company) and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 213, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Code no.1203: American Can Company and United Papermakers and Paper Workers, AFL-CIO, AND International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, 1961-1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Code no.1204: Brown Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 75, 1960-1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Code no.1205: Champion Papers, Inc. and Independent Paper and Pulp Mill Workers AND International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, 1960-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Code no.1206: Consolidated Paper Company and The United Papermakers and Paperworkers, AFL-CIO, Locals 1000, 1004, 1006, 1960- 1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Code no.1207: Consolidated Water Power and Paper Company and The United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 116, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Code no.1209: Great Northern Paper Company and The United Papermakers and Paperworkers; 5 other unions, 1961-1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Code no.1211: Hammermill Paper Company and The United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 620, 1961-1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Code no.1212: Hudson Pulp and Paper Corporation and The United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Locals 565, 717 AND The International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Locals 598, 641, 852, 1961-1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Code no.1213: American Writing Paper Corporation, Franklin Paper Company, National Vulcanized Fiber Company, Valley Paper Company and The United Papermakers and Paperworkers, AFL- CIO, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Code no.1214: International Paper Company and The United Papermakers and Paperworkers, International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1961-1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Code no.1215: International Paper Company and The United Papermakers and Paperworkers, International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1961-1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Code no.1217: Kimberly-Clark Corporation and The United Papermakers and Paperworkers, International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Locals 467, 482, 1961-1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Code no.1218: Kimberly-Clark Corporation and The United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Locals 704, 751, 566. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1960-1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Code no.1219: Kimberly-Clark Corporation and Paper Mill Workers' Union, 1961-1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Code no.1220: KVP Sutherland Corporation and The United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 323, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Code no.1688: Johnson and Johnson Ethicon, Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Code no.1800: The American Oil Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 4-449, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Code no.1801: American Oil Company and Independent Petroleum Workers of America, Local 1 AND National Oil Workers Union, Local 1, 1969- 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Code no.1802: Atlantic Richfield Company and Atlantic Independent Union, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Code no.1803: Cities Service Oil Company and Lake Charles Metal Trades Council, AFL-CIO, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Code no.1804: Continental Oil Company and Independent Oil Workers' Union of Oklahoma, 1960-1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Code no.1806: Gulf Oil Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 4-23, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Code no.1808: Humble Oil and Refining Company AND Enjay Chemical Company and Gulf Coast Industrial Workers' Union, 1969- 1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Code no.1809: Mobil Oil Corporation and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 4-243, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Code no.1811: Shell Oil Company and 11 AFL-CIO Unions, 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Code no.1814: Atlantic Richfield Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Code no.1815: Standard Oil Company of California and International Union of Petroleum Workers, AFL-CIO, 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Code no.1816: Standard Oil Company of California and Oil Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 1-547, 1959- 1971 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Code no.1819: Tidewater Oil Company (Philips Petroleum Company) and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 1-5, 1959-1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Code no.1901: The Dayton Tire and Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1967- 1971 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Code no.1904: General Motors Corporation and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 87, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Code no.1905: General Tire and Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Locals 9, 312, 1967- 1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Code no.1907: The Kelly-Springfield Tire Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 26, 1957- 1970 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Code no.1910: The Mansfield Tire and Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 17, 1960- 1973 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Code no.1912: Uniroyal, Inc. and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Code no.1918: Dayco Southern and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 277, 1961-1971 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Code no.1919: The Gates Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 154, 1961- 1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Code no.1924: Formica Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 757, 1960- 1971 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Code no.1927: Owens-Illinois, Inc. and Glass Bottle Blowers Association of America, AFL-CIO, 1962-1971 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Code no.1930: General Tire and Rubber Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 626, 1963- 1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Code no.1933: The Dunlop Tire and Rubber Corporation and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 135, 1967- 1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Code no.1935: Rubbermaid, Inc. and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 302, 1965-1969 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Code no.2100: A.C. Lawrence Leather Company and Leather Workers' International Union, Local 33, 1960-1970 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Code no.2101: Massachusetts Leather Manufacturers Association and Leather Workers' International Union, Local 21, 1959-1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Code no.561423: Composition Roofers and Waterproofers Employers Association of New York City and Slate Tile and Composition Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers Association, Local 8, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Code no.570329: Basic-Witz Corporation (Skyline Plastics Corporation) and Furniture Workers' Union, Local 2983 AND United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1967-1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Code no.590012: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 2232, 1968-1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Code no.590090: Cleaners and Dyers Board of Trade and Cleaners, Dyers, Pressers, Drivers and Allied Trades Union (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1969-1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Code no.590206: International Smelting and Refining Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 4985, 1959-1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Code no.590240: American Standard, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1199, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Code no.590254: National Tea Company and The Amalgamated Food Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 590, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Code no.590353: Kuner-Empson Company and Warehouse and Distribution Employees Union, Local 452, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Code no.590408: Philco-Ford Corporation and International Union of United Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1430, 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Code no.590495: Wagner Electric Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 322, 1970- 1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Code no.590567: Employers of Metropolitan Chicago and Truck Drivers, Oil Drivers, Filling Station and Platform Workers Union (Teamsters), Local 705, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Code no.590573: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and Laborers' International Union of North America, Local 872, 1970- 1973 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Code no.590607: Loft Candy Corporation, Far Eastern Manufacturing Company and Confectionary Union, AFL-CIO, Local 50, 1967- 1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Code no.590623: Olin Corporation and Allied and Technical Workers of the United States and Canada, Local 14901, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Code no.590710: Oil Transport Company and The Union of Transportation Employees, 1968-1971 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Code no.590772: John Morrell and Company and United Packinghouse, Food and Allied Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1959-1973 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Code no.590779: Chevrolet Dealers of Chicago and Automobile Mechanics, Local 701, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Code no.590781: Great Scoot Food Markets, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 2, 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Code no.590792: Minneapolis-Moline, Inc. (White Motor Corporation) and International Union of United Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Locals 932, 107, 1968-1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Code no.590808: North Electric Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Code no.590827: PPG Industries, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 470, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Code no.590879: National Bellas Hess, Inc. and Office and Professional Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 320, 1968- 1973 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Code no.590901: The General Contractors Association of Louisville, Kentucky and General Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers of America (Teamsters), Local 89, 1968-1973 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Code no.590909: Ice Cream Industry of Philadelphia and Food Driver-Salesmen, Dairy and Ice Cream Workers Union (Teamsters), Locals 463, 331, 1963-1974 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Code no.590925: General Steel Industries, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1022, 1960-1975 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Code no.590954: Associated General Contractors of America and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1966- 1973 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Code no.590991: Univac, Sperry Rand Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Local 1063, 1963-1972 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Code no.591065: Maremont Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, 1965-1972 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Code no.591219: The Green Shoe Manufacturing Company and Boot and Shoe Workers' Union, AFL-CIO, Local 138, 1959-1968 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Code no.591317: Home Builders Association of Metropolitan Portland and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1968- 1974 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Code no.591454: National Electrical Contractors Association (Alameda Section) and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 595, 1967-1971 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Code no.840064: Philadelphia Transportation Company and Transport Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 234, 1953-1973 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Code no.2535: Northwestern Steel and Wire Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1966-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Code no.2537: Pittsburg Coke and Chemical Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Code no.2538: Pittsburg Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Code no.2539: Republic Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Code no.2540: Sharon Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Code no.2541: Superior Tube Company and Superior Tube Employees' Association, 1960-1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Code no.2546: Union Carbide Corporation and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-250, 1960-1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Code no.2547: Union Carbide Corporation and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 3-639, 1960-1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Code no.2548: Union Carbide Corporation and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 3-89, 1960-1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Code no.2550: Cyclops Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1971 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Code no.2551: Wheeling Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Code no.2552: Alan Wood Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Code no.2553: The Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Code no.2554: The Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Code no.2555: American Steel Foundries and United Steelworkers of America, 1957-1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Code no.1260: New York and Pennsylvania Co., Inc. and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, AFL-CIO, Local 701, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Code no.1261: Scott Paper Company and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1961-1971 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Code no.1262: Fraser Paper Limited and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, AFL-CIO, International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Code no.1264: Greater New York Folding Box and Display Manufacturers Association, Inc. and Folding Box, Corrugated Box and Display Workers, Local No. 381, 1964-1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Code no.1265: Philadelphia Container Association and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 375, 1964- 1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Code no.1266: Georgia-Pacific Corporation and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Locals 369, 369a, 1963-1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Code no.1268: American Can Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, 1965- 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Code no.1267: New York and Pennsylvania Co., Inc. and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, AFL-CIO, Locals 787, 788, 1964- 1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Code no.1269: Hudson Pulp and Paper Corporation and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 579, 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)